[Fatima] Previously on Zatima.
I can't believe we got
a little Zac comin'.
[Fatima] What if it's a girl?
Then she'd be called Zatima.
How is this whole
real estate thing?
I mean. it was good. until
he invested our money
in a property we can't afford.
So how much are you in the hole?
Three million dollars.
Damn!
I'm Angela.
-Come on. I know you.
-[Angela] What the hell?!
I'm all over these fetish sites.
It was Bryce. He
said he got hacked.
I think I might know
somebody that can help us.
Remember Leslie? Her
husband works at the FBI.
Zac. these two were in love.
He's still not over you.
What the hell...
Leslie and Zac seem
to be in the way.
I'm gonna get her back.
[Jeremiah] Give me the
fuckin' money. Fatima!
Give me the money!
[Zac] Jeremiah.
you touch my wife?
[Nathan] You're gonna kill him.
[Connie] I went to the doctor.
They said I don't have
a long time to live.
Tony. it's cancer.
[Zac] I just don't
know the first thing
about plannin' a funeral.
-We can do it together. okay?
-[Zac] Yes.
-Because we...
-[Fatima] Ride together.
And we die together.
We're all just here
because we love you. man.
I know we can seem messy and.
you know.
dysfunctional at times.
but this is our crazy.
messy. dysfunctional family
and we wouldn't have
it any other way. bro.
[gunshots]
-Zac...
-[Zac] Get off me!
What is... What
is wrong with you?
-Come on!
-[Man] Yo. what the...?
Where that nigga at?
[serious music]
No. no! Motherfucker!
[Man] Oh. shit!
[tense music]
Fatima...
[serious music]
No. no. move. move.
move. move. move. move!
Baby!
[serious music]
[Zac] Baby. baby!
[Fatima groans]
Uh. call an ambulance!
I'm on it. I'm on it!
Hello? Yes. I need an ambulance.
My girl got shot!
[Zac] You okay?
Where'd he. where'd
he shoot you?
[Fatima] He didn't. Mm...
-[Zac] No?
-No.
-Are you sure?
-I'm sure.
He didn't hit me.
I just slipped.
Okay. I'mma sit you up. okay?
-Mm-mm.
-[Zac] Yes. please.
-You have to sit up. please.
-[Fatima] Okay.
-One. two. three.
-Easy. easy. easy.
[serious music]
[Zac] I'll slide
you back. Ready?
One. two. three. Come on.
Come on. I got you. I got you.
I got you. I got you.
Oh. mm...
-Damn. Zac...
-Yo. he's gone.
[serious music]
I'mma kill that motherfucker.
[Fatima] Zac. no.
What you mean. no?
He just shot at you.
-Ugh. shit!
-[Zac] Whoa. whoa. whoa.
-Oh. God!
-Okay. okay. okay.
Okay. uh. what's.
what's happenin'?
-What's the matter?
-[Angela] She's cramping. Zac.
-Huh?
-She's cramping.
-[Fatima groaning]
-[Zac] Why?
It's too much
stress on the baby.
Okay. um...
Fatima. I'm sorry. I
hope the baby'll be okay.
Hey. get him outta here.
Man. get all these people...
Everybody get the
fuck outta here!
Okay. everybody back up!
Back up. give 'em some space!
[ladies breathing heavily]
♪ Love ain't perfect ♪
♪ But we still workin'
♪ May not be what we see on TV.
but it's damn sure worth it ♪
♪ Uh-huh. love ain't perfect ♪
♪ But we still workin' ♪
♪ Don't gotta be
what we see on IG ♪
♪ 'Cause we still worth it ♪
♪ Uh-huh. yeah. yeah ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Do. do. do. do.
do. do. do. do ♪
♪ We still workin' ♪
[Angela] The ambulance
and the police
should be here any minute.
-What is taking them so long?
-They're coming.
[Zac] Breathe. baby. breathe.
Mm...
Breathe.
Oh God. Zac. I'm scared.
What if I lose the baby?
Shh. don't say that.
don't say that.
Don't say that.
Please don't say that.
-Please.
-Oh my God.
-Zac...
-Yes?
It hurts so bad.
Okay. okay. okay. I
know. I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
What do I do. what do I do?
Just. just keep her calm. okay?
-And stay positive. Fatima.
-Angela. it hurts!
[Fatima groaning]
[ambulance sirens wailing]
Angela. Angela. the
paramedics here.
-[Fatima] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Yes.
I'm scared I'mma lose the baby.
No. you won't. you won't.
you won't. you won't.
I'm here. I'm here.
You're with me.
-[Bryce] She's over there.
-She's pregnant.
and she's in a lot of pain.
[Female EMT] The call said
there's a shooting victim.
That was wrong. but hurry.
She's still in a lot of pain.
Hurry up!
[Female EMT] Excuse
me. let her go.
Let me get her. let me get her.
Hi. how are you feeling?
Tell me what's going on.
There's sharp pains in my side.
It's just cramping really bad.
How's the pain scale?
From one to ten.
Fuckin' ten.
-[Zac] What's wrong with her?
-Oh my God.
What's wrong with her?
[Female EMT] One second.
[serious music]
Her blood pressure is spiking.
we'll have to take her in.
-Alright.
-[Female EMT] Just breathe.
Just breathe for me.
-Zac. don't leave me.
-Oh. I'm not leavin'.
-[Fatima] Zac...
-I'm not.
but I gotta deal
with somethin' first.
[Fatima. weakly] Oh my God...
Jeremiah. why would you?
This is not my fault. niggas!
I didn't know this
shit was gonna happen!
But why would you bring
that shit here. Jeremiah?
Because they was fuckin'
chasin' me and I needed help!
You better calm the fuck down.
You almost got Fatima killed.
Look. your ass need to go.
'cause we cannot protect
you from Zac no more.
[Belinda] Officer.
there he is right there.
He know exactly who
shot at my friend.
I thought y'all wasn't friends.
Why you always worry
about the wrong shit?!
Hey. hey. hey. hey! Hey. hey!
Hey! Come on. man!
[shouting]
I swear on everything.
I swear everything.
it's me and you.
I swear on everything.
[Jeremiah] Sorry. man.
Fuck that! Fuck you. man!
Hey. hey. hey.
hey. hey. hey. hey.
Hey. Look. look. look. look.
We don't need you gettin'
arrested. too. okay?
That's right. save him
from himself. baby!
Okay. what's goin'
on here. Nate?
Look. Swank. that's my brother.
Take his stupid ass to
jail before I kill him.
Man. can somebody tell
me what's goin' on?
Exactly what's going on?
I got you Swank. alright?
So. this nigga was runnin'
from another nigga.
And that nigga tried to
shoot this nigga and missed.
and almost hit his girl.
-What?
-Come on. Swank.
[Tony] Oh my God.
Sir. are you intoxicated?
Intoxi-what?
Officer. he stole somethin' from
the man that y'all lookin' for.
Sir. you stealin' somethin'?
Mm-hm. yeah.
[Jeremiah] I ain't
got nothin'. man.
[serious music]
Sir. I gotta take you in.
Man. I stole a
stupid-ass chain. man.
That nigga wouldn't
give me my dope. man!
Take his stupid ass.
Safer than bein' here.
Sorry. man. I really am.
Jeremiah. I don't wanna
see you ever again. bro.
Never.
[serious music]
[Zac] Stupid. Come on.
Swank. I'mma call you.
Alright. I got you.
[Zac] Hey. hey.
hey. hey. hey. hey.
-Hey.
-Baby. I'm scared.
No. you good. you good. Hey.
Hey. so. can you
take care of this?
Of course. of course.
Can I. can I ride with her?
[gentle music]
[Zac] Go on. go ahead.
I'll stay back and clean up.
[Fatima crying] Zac...
[Zac] I'm comin'. I'm comin'.
I got you.
[emotional music]
Okay. everybody needs to go.
-Now.
-[Nathan] Alright.
[Tony] Come on.
let's go. Come on.
Please...
Shit...
[emotional music]
[door closing]
Uh. that was crazy.
Yeah. it was.
Do you want me to stay
with you for protection?
[serious music]
Bryce...
[Bryce] What?
Angela. you saw
what just happened.
Yeah. I saw it.
but I'm good. okay?
I mean. do you. you don't
think I can protect you?
[serious music]
It's not that I
think that. Bryce.
I just don't need you
to protect me. okay?
But I will.
Yeah. I'm sure. Okay?
But you can go home.
[serious music]
Okay.
[door closing]
[crickets chirping]
[serious music]
Okay. it looks like we've got
your blood pressure and
heart rate stabilized.
Um. what about the baby?
Same with the baby.
but we wanna keep Fatima here
overnight just to monitor her.
That was quite a scare.
Yeah.
The main thing is we wanna keep
her as stress free as possible.
Okay.
I mean. stress can take
a toll on really anyone.
especially a pregnant woman.
[emotional music]
Alright. well. you won't
have to worry about that.
I'll make sure nobody
stresses her out.
I got you.
Just make sure you
don't stress me out
tryin' not to stress me out.
[Dr. Harris] Well. I
am serious. Fatima.
I need you to take it easy.
I hear you. Doctor.
Good.
Well. I'll be back with
the blood work results
in about an hour.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Thank you.
[Zac] Thank you.
[emotional music]
Zac. why are you pacing?
Thinkin'.
Zac. I need you to promise me
you're not gonna
do anything crazy.
You always tellin' me not
to do something crazy.
and forgive Jeremiah.
Look at this shit. Look at it.
But Zac. he didn't shoot at me.
He brought the nigga into our...
[serious music]
He brought that man
in our house who did.
[serious music]
Alright. you know what?
I get it. I get it.
I mean. if you wanna cut him
off for good. I understand.
Cut him off? I'm gonna bury him.
Zac...
I don't know. Fatima.
That. that's it.
this the last time.
If I ever see that nigga
again. it's on sight.
[serious music]
I get it.
Do you?
Yes.
Look. because of Jeremiah.
me and the baby
could've died tonight.
But baby. if you do something.
you're taking yourself
away from us. too.
And Zac. I need you.
-I know.
-No. I really need you.
I know. Fatima. but I
can't let somebody hurt you
and do nothing about it.
Zac. I'm not asking you
to do nothing. okay?
I'm just asking you
not to do somethin'
that's gonna have me
bringin' our child
to see his or her
father through a glass.
Let's just hope Jeremiah
stays away for good this time.
You right. you right.
I gotta do somethin'.
but I can't just hope.
I'm gonna get you
some protection.
What? Zac. I got
a gun. I'm good.
[Zac] I'm not talkin'
about the gun.
I'm getting you a bodyguard.
A bodyguard?
Yeah.
This way. if I'm not around.
you're still protected.
Zac...
I don't know why I ain't
think about this before.
Baby. I'm not Beyoncé. I do
not need a bodyguard. okay?
You need somethin'.
-Zac...
-[Zac] No. it just makes sense.
Think about it.
if I'm not there.
then you get protected at home.
at work. and at the store.
-Like...
-Okay. you know what?
This right here will be
considered too much. okay?
It's too much?
-Yes.
-[Zac] You stressed?
Zac. I cannot have a bodyguard
follow me around everywhere.
Especially not work.
But...
-Fatima...
-[Fatima] Look. Zac. no.
You are enough. okay?
You keep me safe.
I don't feel like I do.
Baby. I don't want
a bodyguard. Okay?
I can't...
[Fatima sighing]
-Okay.
-'Kay.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
[Zac's phone buzzes]
Shoot.
Nathan. Tony. and
Belinda are here.
You wanna talk to 'em?
I'm tryin' to stay
stress-free. remember?
No.
Alright.
I'll tell them you're okay.
[Fatima] Alright.
-[Zac] I'll be back.
-Okay.
-I love you.
-[Fatima] I love you. too.
[gentle music]
[phone buzzing]
Hey.
[Belinda] Hey.
Y'all at the hospital yet?
Yeah. we're still
here. Zac text Nathan
and said she's still in there
dealin' with the doctor.
Still?
Oh my God. I hope
nothin' bad happened.
I can't take that.
Yeah. you and me both.
You know. we just
gotta pray. okay?
I am prayin'.
While I'm cleanin' up
this mess everybody left.
You're a good friend for that.
[Angela] Yeah.
And maybe Fatima will see
that you're makin' an effort.
I really hope so. Angela.
Like. I really am sorry.
That shit was scary.
Seein' her on the ground
like that. thinkin' that...
I didn't have another
chance with her. you know?
Belinda. you gotta
tell her that.
Girl. I really hurt her.
She ain't tryin' to hear me.
[Angela] You just gotta
give it some time.
What you did was really foul.
but just keep trying. okay?
I'm not gon' give up. you know?
A good friend wouldn't.
Alright. um...
I'mma call you when
Zac come back in
and tell us what the
doctor said. alright?
Okay. thank you.
[Belinda] Bye.
[serious music]
You hear anything from him?
Oh. there he is.
[Tony] Hey. how is she?
The baby okay?
She's good.
Oh. thank God.
The baby good. too.
Thank you.
[Zac] She. um...
She was stressed out.
Her levels were elevated.
so caused the cramping.
They gotta keep her overnight.
Oh. good. Okay.
I'm. I'mma go call Angela and
tell her the good news. okay?
Alright.
[serious music]
[Nathan sighing]
The fuck is she here for?
She followed me. man.
Hey. Zac. just...
How are you feeling. man?
I'm messed up. bro.
Like. I wanna wring
Jeremiah's neck.
I ain't never wanna
end somebody so bad.
Yo. hey. hey. bro.
You gotta calm down
with this anger. man.
It'll eat you up inside.
I know. I just don't
know what to do.
Zac. you just gotta make sure
you and Fatima and the baby
are all safe - I know.
but she won't let me!
Nah. man. hey.
You. you lookin'
at it all wrong.
She won't let you throw
your life away. you know?
She love you. man. and Jeremiah
ain't worth goin' to
prison over forever.
Yeah. I mean. if he
comes to her again.
-We'll just...
-I don't know
what I will do. bro.
-on everything.
-Hey. hey. I get that.
We get that. we understand that.
Zac. man. you don't
want killin' somebody
to be on your conscience.
It's some heavy shit.
[serious music]
Uh. I mean. um...
I'm just saying we're gonna
do our best. you know.
to keep him away from you.
You know?
How. Tony?
I don't know. you might
have to. you know.
move and change your
name or something.
That man a
crack-diggity-head. Tony.
He gon' find Zac
regardless. alright?
Listen. Tony. I'm
not changin' my name.
and I'm not moving.
He ain't the mafia.
Um. Angela was really glad that
Fatima and the baby are okay.
[Nathan] That's good.
You alright. Zac?
Don't start. Belinda.
Well. I can't even ask
you if you alright?
Damn!
Look. we've been
through a lot. alright?
After everything
that happened today.
you think we could just
put all that behind us?
Look. he's focused on not
killing Jeremiah right now.
Oh. well. I wouldn't
blame him for doing that.
-Oh...
-Thank you.
Don't egg him on.
[Belinda] Right.
Zac. you should not
go kill Jeremiah.
-[Nathan] Thank you.
-Even if that nigga deserved it.
[Nathan] Belinda!
What?
You wouldn't want vengeance
if it was me. nigga?
-Hell no!
-[Belinda] Okay. see?
That's why you need to
go back to your wife!
-[Belinda & Nathan arguing]
-Hey. hey. hey!
Can we get back to
makin' sure that
Fatima and the baby
are okay. please?
Right. right?
Bro. we really did just come
here to check on you and Fatima.
I'm good.
I'm not goin' nowhere. I'mma
stay with Fatima tonight.
-Good. 'cause she needs you.
-[Zac] I know.
And the baby needs you.
I know. I know. I know.
He could outsource it.
Belinda. are you for
real? Outsource it?
Belinda. come on!
He don't wanna do nothin'
that gon' get his hands dirty
and take him away from
Fatima and the baby!
It would crush her.
I know. It's the most
frustrating thing.
[Nathan] Whoa. whoa.
whoa. well. look.
Hey. it's okay. You
stayin' here tonight.
So. you ain't gotta
worry about that. right?
Yeah. but what about
tomorrow night?
And the next day
and the day after?
Hey. hey. come on. like. I
don't need this right now.
I'm doin' my best
to keep it together.
She don't want me to do
nothin'. I won't do nothin'.
But I'm tellin' y'all. if
I see that nigga again.
it's over.
I understand.
We understand.
I'm out.
Aight. man.
'Kay. we'll catch you
in the morning. aight?
-I love you.
-[Tony] I love you too. man.
Take care of her.
[serious music]
[Belinda & Nathan arguing]
Yo. yo...
[serious music]
Hey.
Oh. man.
[serious music]
What's up?
Nothing.
Tony and Nathan good?
Yeah. They good.
They asked about
you and the baby.
I told them you were
good. so they fine.
Belinda was concerned.
Mm. she was just bein' nosy.
Nah. she looked a
little shook up.
[emotional music]
I'm sure it scared her.
Baby. it scared everybody.
Especially me.
I know. baby.
Damn.
What?
Your parents gonna go
crazy when they find out.
Oh shit. yeah. we
cannot tell my dad.
He would never let this go.
You serious?
Zac. yes!
Look. you just got
on his good side.
My mama's still side-eyeing you.
How they still...?
We about to have a baby.
y'all. They gotta chill.
Chill?
Zac. I just got shot at.
[emotional music]
Yo. they ain't gonna never
forgive me when they find out.
Baby. you cannot keep blaming
yourself for this. okay?
It's not your fault.
Fatima. you have no idea
what it's like bein' a man.
I know. Zac. but you cannot
keep blaming yourself
for Jeremiah's ass.
I can't blame myself. but I
gotta take some of the blame.
Think about it. if
somethin' happened to you.
you best believe people
gonna be lookin' at me.
and saying. "Why didn't
you protect her?"
Yeah. I get it. I get it.
Yeah. that's why we
cannot tell my parents.
And that's why Jeremiah
need to stay away forever.
And how you plan on
makin' that happen?
I don't know. But I will.
See. your ass gon'
end up back in jail.
I already know it.
Fatima. that's the
only way I know.
[Fatima] No it's not. Zac.
Yes. it is.
You do know there's
another way to handle this.
I know my way.
No.
Aight. So. what you
want me to do then?
Let it go. babe.
[scoffs. chuckles]
Let it go?
[Fatima] Yes!
Zac. let it go.
Look. the baby's doin'
good and growing.
and we're doin' so good.
Look. if we wake up
livin' every day in fear.
we'll never be happy.
[emotional music]
Fatima. if somethin'
happened to you. man.
I'd never forgive myself.
Zac. I'm not sayin'
nothing's gonna happen.
I'd be lyin'.
But I don't wanna live in
fear. That's miserable.
Yeah. fear is stressful.
Yes. it is stressful.
[serious music]
And so is anger.
-Alright. I got you.
-[Fatima] Mm-hm.
So. if Jeremiah does
come back around...
Fatima...
Then we will handle
it together. Alright?
But in the meantime.
let's just focus on our child
and building the
life of our dreams.
Okay?
I like that.
Right?
-[Zac] Yeah.
-Yeah.
I'mma build the best
life for you two.
Zac. you already are.
And you're gonna be
an amazing father.
Man...
[emotional music]
I've never been here
for all of this.
Yo. I've never even
seen a birth before.
Well. you get to now.
But you won't if you do
something to Jeremiah
or somebody else.
[gentle music]
You right.
I know I'm right.
[gentle music]
So. how about this?
[Fatima] Hm?
How 'bout you let me
plan the baby shower?
Wait...
You wanna plan the baby shower?
Yeah. I mean. at least
it'll keep my mind off of...
Mm-mm. don't even say his name.
I don't even wanna say his name.
Okay. yeah. you can
plan the baby shower.
-Yes!
-But...
"Yes. but" what?
-I know there's a but.
-Yes.
-There is a but.
-"Yes. but" what?
Zac. nothing crazy
over-the-top. okay?
Me. crazy?
[Fatima] You. yes.
I just want a small.
intimate gathering
with close family and friends.
Oh. and I already
got the color scheme
picked out. so...
Hey. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
You gon' let me plan
this baby shower or what?
Yeah. yeah. You got it.
Okay. so if that's the case.
then you gon' have to let go.
[laughs]
Wow. okay. so you're using
my words against me now.
No. no. no. no. I'm not.
I'm not using your
words against you.
But I gotta make sure you
practice what you preach.
Yeah.
Well. I guess if you can
let go of somethin' so big.
I can let you plan the baby
shower all on your own.
Good.
Just run all the
major things by me.
like the cake. the
invitation list. the venue.
All. you know. all
the major stuff. yeah.
Nope.
[laughs]
Alright. you know what?
You got it. Papa.
Oh. I'm Papa now? I'm a Papa?
What do you wanna be called?
[laid back music]
How 'bout...
Zaddy Zac?
No. Zac. no.
-No. Zac.
-Okay.
We got your blood work back.
Oh. okay.
Your cortisol levels are high.
but that's because
of the stressors
you experienced tonight.
Um. how does that
affect the baby?
Well. right now everything
with the baby is going well.
That's great. okay.
But we do wanna keep
you in a relaxed state.
I want you resting tonight.
Okay.
[Dr. Harris] So. you should
be good to go by morning.
but I'm telling you.
If you don't keep your
stress levels down.
I'm afraid you'll be
assigned bed rest.
Wait. Bed rest?
Doc. I gotta work.
[Dr. Harris] Well.
you're okay for now.
But stress can affect the
baby's brain development.
among other things.
-Can't have that.
-[Dr. Harris] Right.
Right.
[Dr. Harris] So. we'll be
releasing you in the morning.
and I want you to follow up
with your OB within a week.
She will.
Okay. alright. great.
You get some rest. Fatima.
-Okay.
-And you're safe.
-Thank you. Doctor.
-[Zac] Thank you. Doc.
[calm music]
Bed rest?
You gotta listen to
what these doctors say.
Zac. look. I can't
take off of work.
Yo. relax.
Work is the last
thing you should be
stressed about right now.
Yeah. easy for you to say.
You make your own schedule.
Alright. it's alright.
Just don't even think about
it. don't worry about it.
I know. I just...
[serious music]
I don't wanna lose my job. Zac.
Hey. hey. relax. You
not on bed rest yet.
Yeah. but I gotta
stay stress free
so that I don't get on bed rest.
Okay. and if you do. I got you.
[serious music]
Zac. I love my job.
Okay. so. what?
Stay-at-home Fatima
ain't on the table?
Stay at home and do what?
Be a mom and a wife.
Zac. no. I can't think
about that right now.
Besides. I'm already
planning maternity leave.
Okay. okay. relax.
Hey. hey. hey. relax.
Breathe. Can we breathe?
[laid back music]
How they do it?
[Zac] No? That's
not how they do it?
Kind of. but no.
Okay. what. what. what will
make you relax tonight?
Mm. some ice cream.
That would do it. yeah.
Ice cream? The
cafeteria not even open.
Um. I'm sure you'll find it.
You're very resourceful.
Ah-ha. I get it.
You sending me on a
bum mission. right?
So that I get out your
face. That's what you doin'?
No. I'm keeping you
from stressing me out.
and also testing you to
see if you can let it go.
Okay. cool.
I got you. I'mma go
get your ice cream.
Thank you. baby.
Soon as I get of
these security guards
to sit outside your room.
Really. Zac?
It's not that serious.
I'm just serious.
[laid back music]
Oh my God.
[line trilling]
Hello? Security?
Yeah. I need two.
and I mean two guards
outside of 427. pronto.
Yes. sir. Alright.
I'll be outside.
[Fatima] Mm.
I love you.
Mm-hm.
I'm gettin' ice cream.
Thank you.
Security!
I said two!
[laid back music]
[eerie music]
[screams]
Shit. Fatima! What...?
[eerie music]
Uh... You're not Fatima.
My goodness. I didn't realize
anybody was still here.
Yeah. I'm here. ho.
So. why are you breaking
into my girl's house?
You know. I saw the
lights were off outside
and Zac's car was gone. so...
You're not explaining
fast enough. okay?
And if you don't. I'mma dropkick
your ass outta here. so...
I just came to check on Fatima.
You know. she's been
so scared ever since
that situation
with Zac's brother.
Oh.
[Leslie] So. I just
wanted to check on her.
make sure she's all good.
in the event that. you
know. Zac's gone...
She's not here.
and Zac's not here.
I'm here. Her best friend.
Yeah. I remember.
She always says such
wonderful things about you.
Yeah. and she asked
you to check on her?
Yeah. she gave me a
key and everything.
She gave you a key?
Yes.
Really?
Yeah. that's how I got in.
That's all.
Okay.
But. you know.
since you're here.
I see everything's
under control.
so I can just give
Fatima a call.
She's at the hospital.
Why. is everything okay?
She's fine. but since y'all
are such good friends.
I'll let you talk about it.
Right.
Of course. I'll just
give her a call.
-Mm-hm.
-[Leslie] Bye. Angela.
-Bye.
-It's always so good seeing you.
[Angela] I bet.
[mysterious music]
[door opens and shuts]
What the hell was that?
[music]